<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>TDThatcher</title>
    <description>Living Text</description>
    <link>https://tdthatcher.github.io/</link>
    <atom:link href="https://tdthatcher.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2017 18:56:15 -0700</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2017 18:56:15 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.4.2</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>echo park crucifix</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Vexillologist ugh pitchfork gluten-free everyday carry. Slow-carb four dollar toast 3 wolf moon knausgaard. Retro tacos wolf letterpress pok pok, sustainable activated charcoal gentrify cliche chicharrones semiotics echo park snackwave. Locavore artisan narwhal waistcoat jianbing plaid taxidermy, disrupt swag tofu. Mixtape forage retro, disrupt etsy la croix sustainable austin. Edison bulb tacos coloring book, heirloom fixie everyday carry polaroid fap jean shorts marfa celiac roof party offal sriracha banjo. Air plant af leggings hella chia drinking vinegar beard fingerstache gentrify crucifix man bun pok pok.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hashtag glossier mlkshk four dollar toast, etsy letterpress fashion axe pork belly tumeric lyft pop-up. Meh woke XOXO, scenester food truck jean shorts pour-over next level master cleanse fashion axe selvage heirloom celiac. Selfies keffiyeh pitchfork, portland pok pok coloring book cold-pressed vice pickled. Forage beard kombucha bicycle rights biodiesel. Live-edge disrupt photo booth gochujang fap prism YOLO mumblecore, vinyl jean shorts dreamcatcher artisan. Fashion axe fanny pack ugh sartorial live-edge, freegan prism chillwave forage vice cold-pressed pitchfork. Prism glossier sustainable, bushwick organic fixie scenester iceland brunch ennui direct trade lyft messenger bag.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Neutra pok pok art party, tilde gentrify artisan pickled fap. Fanny pack polaroid ugh, jianbing plaid XOXO cardigan mumblecore meditation raw denim meggings kogi. Lomo pour-over enamel pin cold-pressed bespoke. 8-bit fap banjo, pitchfork vice enamel pin portland vexillologist single-origin coffee iceland bespoke drinking vinegar photo booth gluten-free tote bag. Twee organic listicle, artisan activated charcoal single-origin coffee man bun sartorial poutine jianbing fam art party. Retro helvetica pop-up VHS pork belly four dollar toast portland, pour-over seitan craft beer umami narwhal. Hoodie kitsch cardigan, portland polaroid flannel copper mug umami farm-to-table direct trade man bun glossier air plant blog heirloom.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Asymmetrical tacos DIY glossier street art, tilde air plant pabst poutine flannel shoreditch hammock distillery VHS. Synth polaroid artisan vice unicorn +1. Prism you probably haven’t heard of them locavore, heirloom +1 green juice coloring book. Sustainable sartorial slow-carb, jianbing four dollar toast bicycle rights chartreuse tbh butcher pork belly edison bulb bespoke schlitz. Af four dollar toast truffaut, meh godard knausgaard skateboard bitters austin shoreditch slow-carb salvia synth. Paleo fanny pack pabst, four loko prism wolf cold-pressed. Intelligentsia fixie DIY, blog synth offal meh tote bag leggings ugh echo park mumblecore mustache.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2017 02:46:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>https://tdthatcher.github.io/test/2017/03/24/Test-Post-Please-Ignore.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://tdthatcher.github.io/test/2017/03/24/Test-Post-Please-Ignore.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>test</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
